<?xml version = "1.0" encoding ="UTF-8" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="RAPI.xsl"?>
<application><doc>Completing the First Steps Setup</doc>
<resources base="">
<resource path="https://{appliance_hostname}/setup_complete">
<param type="path" name="appliance_hostname">
<doc>Host name of the appliance.</doc>
</param>
<method name="PUT" id="Completing the First Steps Setup Docker"><doc> The first steps setup contains system level web services and configuration that must be completed before using the appliance. </doc>
<doc> The first required step is to ensure that you have agreed to the Service Agreements. Requests to all configuration APIs will redirect to the Service Agreements API until it has been agreed to. </doc>
<doc> &#009;&#8226; First Steps > Service Agreements </doc>
<doc> Once the Service Agreements step is completed, the First Steps Setup can be completed using the API described on this page. </doc>
<doc> Optionally, the following APIs can also be used during the First Steps Setup: </doc>
<doc> &#009;&#8226; Manage: System Settings > System Settings > Administrator Settings </doc>
<doc> To complete the First Steps Setup process, issue a PUT request to the setup complete endpoint. </doc>
<doc> The LMI will restart automatically if required. If the LMI will not restart automatically, a response body containing lmi_restart with the value of 'false' is returned. </doc>
<request>
<doc>PUT https://{appliance_hostname}/setup_complete</doc><param name="Accept" style="header">
<doc>application/json </doc></param>
</request>
<response status="200">
<doc>Success</doc>
<doc>If no LMI restart is required:
 200 OK
 {&quot;lmi_restart&quot;: false}

 If an LMI restart is NOT required, this web service will return no body.
 200 OK
 no json body</doc><representation name="FirstStepsCompleteRestart" mediatype="application/json">
<param style="plain" name="lmi_restarting" type="Boolean" optional="No" >
<doc>If the LMI does not need to restart, this parameter will be returned with a value of false. If the LMI is restarting, the response will contain no JSON body. </doc>
</param>
</representation></response><response status="302">
<doc>If the service agreement has not yet been accepted, this API will return a redirect to the Service Agreements endpoint.</doc>
<doc>HTTP/1.1 302 Found
 ...
 Location: https://{appliance_hostname}/setup_service_agreements</doc></response></method>
</resource>
</resources>
</application>
