<?xml version = "1.0" encoding ="UTF-8" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="RAPI.xsl"?>
<application><doc>Viewing the runtime environment configuration status</doc>
<resources base="">
<resource path="https://{appliance_hostname}/isam/runtime_components/">
<param type="path" name="appliance_hostname">
<doc>Host name of the appliance.</doc>
</param>
<method name="GET" id="Viewing the runtime environment configuration status"><doc>     To retrieve the runtime environment status with the RESTful web service, issue an HTTP GET command on the runtime environment resource URI. </doc>
<request>
<doc>
 GET https://{appliance_hostname}/isam/runtime_components
 </doc><param name="Authorization" style="header">
<doc>Basic Authentication header </doc></param>
<param name="Accept:application/json" style="header">
<doc>Required for requests to the service </doc></param>
</request>
<response status="400">
<doc>There is a problem with the request. The JSON message describes the problem.</doc>
<param name="Content-Type:application/json" style="header">
<doc>Response is in JSON formatting </doc></param>
<representation name="httpErrorJsonResponse" mediatype="application/json">
<param style="plain" name="message" type="String" optional="No" >
<doc>The error message. </doc>
</param>
</representation></response><response status="404">
<doc>File not Found, The requested service does not exist. The JSON message indicates which resource.</doc>
<param name="Content-Type:application/json" style="header">
<doc>Response is in JSON formatting </doc></param>
<representation name="httpErrorJsonResponse" mediatype="application/json">
<param style="plain" name="message" type="String" optional="No" >
<doc>The error message. </doc>
</param>
</representation></response><response status="500">
<doc>An internal error occurred. The JSON message indicates the problem.</doc>
<param name="Content-Type:application/json" style="header">
<doc>Response is in JSON formatting </doc></param>
<representation name="httpErrorJsonResponse" mediatype="application/json">
<param style="plain" name="message" type="String" optional="No" >
<doc>The error message. </doc>
</param>
</representation></response><response status="200">
<doc>OK, The request was successful.</doc>
<doc>
 200 ok

 [{
 "id":"RTE",
 "status":"Available",
 "statuscode":"0",
 "mode":"Local Standalone",
 "modecode":"1"
 }]
 </doc><param name="Content-Type:application/json" style="header">
<doc>Response is in JSON formatting </doc></param>
<representation name="viewRTEConfigStatusJsonResponse" mediatype="application/json">
<param style="plain" name="id" type="String" optional="No" >
<doc>The identifier for the runtime component. The value is always RTE.</doc>
</param>
<param style="plain" name="status" type="String" optional="No" >
<doc>The status of the runtime component. Valid values are Available, Unconfigured, or Not available.</doc>
</param>
<param style="plain" name="statuscode" type="String" optional="No" >
<doc>A code that represents the status of the runtime component. Valid values are: 0: Indicates that the status of the runtime component is Available. 1: Indicates that the status of the runtime component is Unconfigured. 2: Indicates that the status of the runtime component is Not available.</doc>
</param>
<param style="plain" name="mode" type="String" optional="No" >
<doc>The configured mode for the runtime component. Note: When the mode is Local Standalone or Remote Standalone: The Verify Identity Access policies cannot be distributed between different appliances. The clustering capability is limited to instances that are located on the same appliance. Valid values are: Unconfigured Remote: Policy server is remote. Local Standalone: Policy server and LDAP are local. Remote Standalone: Policy server is local and LDAP is remote.</doc>
</param>
<param style="plain" name="modecode" type="String" optional="No" >
<doc>A code that represents the configured mode of the runtime component Note: When the modecode is 1 or 2: The Verify Identity Access policies cannot be distributed between different appliances. The clustering capability is limited to instances that are located on the same appliance. Valid values are: -1: Indicates that the configured mode of the runtime component is Unconfigured. 0: Indicates that the configured mode of the runtime component is Remote. 1: Indicates that the configured mode of the runtime component is Local Standalone. 2: Indicates that the configured mode of the runtime component is Remote Standalone. </doc>
</param>
</representation></response></method>
</resource>
</resources>
</application>
