<?xml version = "1.0" encoding ="UTf-8" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="RAPI.xsl"?>
<application><doc>Widget Filter Search</doc>
<resources base="">
<resource path="http(s)://hostname:port/itim/rest/services">
<param type="query" name="attributes">
<doc>Optional&#58; Specifies the attribute that must be returned as part of search. Only one attribute can be specified. If you specify a comma-separated list of attributes, then no attributes are returned. Example - ?attributes=cn</doc>
</param>
<param type="query" name="limit">
<doc>Optional&#58; Specifies the maximum number of items that the search returns. Example. ?limit=1000</doc>
</param>
<method name="GET" id="Widget Filter Search"><doc>  Returns the search results that are based on the filter configured for a widget . This API is used with the form template REST API. IBM Security Identity Manager forms consist of some widgets that contain an LDAP search filter that is configured by System Administrator. </doc>
<doc>  This configured search filter is returned by "form tempalate" REST API in an encrypted format. The LDAP search API decrypts this filter and returns the search result.  </doc>
<request>
<doc>

 GET https://hostname:port/itim/rest/entities?container;x-link=/itim/rest/services/ZXJnbG9iYWxpZD0yNDk5MjQwO
 TM3NjU5MjI3NzYzLG91PXNlcnZpY2VzLGVyZ2xvYmFsaWQ9MDAwMDAwMDAwMDAwMDAwMDAwMDAsb3U9b3JnLGRjPWNvbQ
        
 </doc><doc>DEPENDENT API : Form Template Lookup</doc><param name="com.ibm.isim.rest.accesstoken" style="header">
<doc>This mandatory header parameter contains the encrypted filter on which search is executed. This token is generated by the "form template" REST API. </doc></param>
<param name="Cache-Control" style="header">
<doc>Optional&#58; Specifies caching options. By default, search results are cached for each client so that subsequent requests by the client that specify the same search criteria are satisfied via the cache. The 'no-cache' option performs the search without referencing any cache. The 'delete-cache' option deletes the cache. In this case, empty search results are returned. Example - Cache-Control=no-cache </doc></param>
<param name="Range" style="header">
<doc>Optional&#58; Specifies the range of items to be returned. Note &#58; The range uses a zero-based index. Example - items=0-99 </doc></param>
</request>
<response status="200">
<doc>OK. The request was successful.</doc>
<doc>
 [
     {
       "_attributes": {
         "cn": "Alan Smith"
       },
       "_id": "ZXJnbG9iYWxpZD0yNDk5MjUzNTY5NjU4OTcxMTg1LG91PTAsb3U9cGVvcGxlLGVyZ2xvYmFsaWQ9MDAwM
       DAwMDAwMDAwMDAwMDAwMDAsb3U9b3JnLGRjPWNvbQ"
     },
     {
       "_attributes": {
         "cn": "Chuck Riegle"
       },
       "_id": "ZXJnbG9iYWxpZD0yNDk5MjUzNTc0NjU3MTkyNzM2LG91PTAsb3U9cGVvcGxlLGVyZ2xvYmFsaWQ9MDAwMDAwM
       DAwMDAwMDAwMDAwMDAsb3U9b3JnLGRjPWNvbQ"
     },
     {
       "_attributes": {
         "cn": "Dan Gosling"
       },
       "_id": "ZXJnbG9iYWxpZD0yNDk5MjU0NjU2NjczNDE2OTMwLG91PTAsb3U9cGVvcGxlLGVyZ2xvYmFsaWQ9MDAwMDAwMDAwMD
       AwMDAwMDAwMDAsb3U9b3JnLGRjPWNvbQ"
     },
     {
       "_attributes": {
         "cn": "Danny Guthrie"
       },
       "_id": "ZXJnbG9iYWxpZD0yNDk5MjU0OTg3MjMzOTU0NjEyLG91PTAsb3U9cGVvcGxlLGVyZ2xvYmFsaWQ9MDAwMDAwMDAwMD
       AwMDAwMDAwMDAsb3U9b3JnLGRjPWNvbQ"
     }
   ]
 </doc></response></method>
</resource>
</resources>
</application>
